[TOILET FLUSHES]
(Leonard:)He offered to send you
to the North Pole?
(Leonard:)Yes.
In fact, he was quite enthusiastic.
He said, "Frankly,
if I could send you tonight, I would."
Okay. Well, do you wanna go?
(Sheldon:)Of course not.
I'm a theoretical physicist.
(Sheldon:)A career I chose in no small part
because it's indoors.
(Sheldon:)But if I'm able to detect slow-moving
magnetic monopoles there...
(Sheldon:)...I will be the scientist
who confirmed string theory.
And people will write books about me.
Third graders will create macaroni-art
dioramas depicting scenes from my life.
(Leonard:)Sure. Maybe a tableau of me
trying to pummel you to death.
(Sheldon:)Sarcasm?
(Leonard:)Maybe.
I am on the horns of a dilemma.
(Sheldon:)Can you imagine me, Sheldon Cooper,
at the North Pole?
(Leonard:)Easy peasy. I'm doing it right now.
(Sheldon:)I'm not good with cold, Leonard.